Guide to the Tom Law San Francisco Bay Area Punk and Rock Handbill and Poster Collection M1976
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters, 3 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes and 1 large map folder
  - Folder 8, 1984- 1986 (Box 4)
    17. Michael Covino, Aaron Noble, Steve Salmons, Harvey Stein, Anita Valerio, Marshall Weber; Artists' Television Access (ATA); 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-27; 8.5x14.
    18. Ha Ha; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-05; 11x17.
    19. San Francisco Science Fiction. SF/SF Party To NYC. New SRL Video: an Epidemic Of Fear; Martin/Weber Gallery; 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-31; 11x17.
    20. Science Presents Future; Giftcenter Pavilion; 888 Brannan St. San Francisco, CA; 1985; 11x17.
    21. Us Girls; Trocadero Transfer; 520 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-30; 11x17.
    22. 700 Club, Ulterior Motives, Vice Grip; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-07; 11x17.
  - Folder 9, 1984- 1986 (Box 4)
    1. Kyllerz, Renata, World's Fastest Female Guitarist; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; August 11; 11x17.
    2. Saint's Ball (Members From Eyes Of God); Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-21; 11x17.
    3. [calendar]; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    4. [calendar]; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04; 11x17.
    5. [calendar]; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    6. Mapenzi; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-19; 11x17.
    7. 700 Club; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-29; 11x17.
    8. Yo; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-16; 11x17.
    9. Mapenzi; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-02; 11x15.5
    10. Mapenzi; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-24; 11x17.
    11. Mapenzi; Vision; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-24; 11x17.
    12. Mapenzi, Too Much Fun; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-23; 11x17.
    13.Mapenzi; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-03; 11x17.
    14. Mapenzi, Joni Haastrup And Friends; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-08; 11x17.
    15. The Looters; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-19; 11x17.
    16. Big City, Mapenzi; Great American Music Hall; 859 O'Farrell St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-21; 11x17.
    17. My Sin; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-14 -- My Sin; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-15 -- My Sin; V.I.,S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-22; 11x17.
    18. My Sin, Necropolis Of Love, Monkey Rhythm; Victoria Theatre; 2961 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-01; 11x17.
    19. It Is A Scandal And Hardly Anybody Seems To Care [with quote from letter from Herb Caen to Mark Anstendig dated 9/27/85 re: acoustics of Davies Hall] San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    20. Culturcide, Problemist, Healers; The Lab [Co-Lab]; 1805 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-18; 11x17.
  - Folder 1, 1984- 1986 (Box 5)
    1. Rockalypse; San Francisco, CA; December 1-January 1; 11x17.
    2. Voice Farm, Impulse F; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-05; 11x17.
    3. Unfinished Business; Theatre Rhinoceros; 2926 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1983; 11x17.
    4. Dogtown; Berkeley Square; 1333 University Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1984-08-22 -- Dogtown; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-24; 1984-08-23 -- Dogtown; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-23 -- Dogtown; Castro Fair; San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-19; 11x17.
    5. The Cocktail Twins; Club 181; 181 Eddy St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-25; 11x17.
    6. Conjunto Cespedes; 16th Note/Firehouse 7; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-09; 11x17.
    7. Richard Howell, Sudden Changes; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; January 10; 11x17.
    8. Benjamin Bossi, Norman Salant, Stouthearted; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-03; 11x17.
    9. Abandon Demand, Debora Iyall; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-03; 11x17.
    10. Buffalo Roam; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; May 11; 11x15.
    11. The 12 Year Olds, The Dave, Cheap Talk W/ Richard D'Arch, Alex Son Of Jack, [Plus Other Major Recording Artists]; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-15; 11x17.
    12. The Cat Heads, Blue Movie, The Furies, [& Various and Sundry Gnarly Cohorts!]; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-06; 11x17.
    13. Hans Naughty, Holy Mary; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-19; 11x17.
    14. [many]; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-18; 11x17.
    15. Flowers Of Pain; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-21; 11x17.
    16. Freaky Executives, Convictions, Crash Groupies; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    17. Club Foot Orchestra; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-24; 11x17.
    18. Crawl Away Machine; Berkeley Square; 1333 University Ave. Berkeley, CA; February 20 -- Crawl Away Machine; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; February 17; 11x17.
    19. Christ On Parade, Clown Alley, Violent Coercion, Rabid Lassie; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-21; 11x17.
    20. Anvil Chorus, Control, Kamikaze; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1984-01-21; 11x17.
  - Folder 2, 1984- 1986 (Box 5)
    1. Fountains Of Use, Sex Gang Children; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-12-05; 11x17.
    2. Skiddoo, Entr'Acte, Andalusian Dog, Ghosts Before Breakfast, News Parade '67; Roxie Theatre; 3117 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-06; 11x17.
    3. Too Much Fun; University of California, Berkeley; Berkeley, CA; 1986-02-28 -- Too Much Fun; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-26; 11x17.
    4. Too Much Fun, African Soundz, Unruly World; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-17; 11x17.
    5. Yanks, Pray For Rain (Formerly Big Race), Flying Color; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; July 3; 11x17.
    6. Usual Suspects; [many, including Mabuhay Gardens, Club Nine, and The Oasis]; [west coast tour]; [many- Thurs. February 20-Tues. February 25 in SF]; 11x17.
    7. The Morlocks, Sea Hags, T.O.T.P., Brotherhood Of Light, DJ Liz Pepin, DJ Cyril Jordan; Swedish-American Hall; 2174 Market St. San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    8. Mental Floss, Club Foot Orchestra, The Rival; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; August 24; 11x17.
    9. Mimi Farina, Katie Webster, Rhiannona, Femprov, Lynn Ray, Blue Jazz Cabaret, Alta Mira, Tommie, Susan Muscarella, Faye Carol Trio; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-28; 11x17.
    10. Us Girls; Trocadero Transfer; 520 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-13; 11x17.
    11. The New Ice Age, Zulu Spear; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-23 -- The New Ice Age, The Looters; Major Pond's; 2801 California St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-22; 11x17.
    12. Too Much Fun; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-28; 11x17.
    13. Too Much Fun; 16th Note/Firehouse 7; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-25 -- Too Much Fun; New College Of California; 777 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-26; 11x17.
    14. Too Much Fun; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-31; 11x17.
    15. Too Much Fun; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-20; 11x17.
    16. Too Much Fun; Last Day Saloon; 406 Clement St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-29; 11x17.
    17. Robyn Hitchcock & The Egyptians, Yo; Berkeley Square; 1333 University Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1985-06-26; 11x17.
    18. Sluglords, Pillage People, Swivel, 11.11, Caroliner Rainbow Family; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-02-14; 10x14.
    19. Esmerelda, Patsy Cline & The Memphis G Spots, Francisco Aguabella & His Bata Drummers, The Newhearts and Pumps, King Rockers; Club Nine; 399 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-13; 11x17.
  - Folder 3, 1985- 1986 (Box 5)
    1. Grand Opening. Used Records And Tapes [etc.]; Reckless; 1401 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    2. Bleeding Catholic Children. A One Act Play, Imperious Music Of Possession, The. Alaric. Paul Hagen; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1986; 11x17.
    3. Register And Ride. '86 AIDS Bike-A-Thon. 25 Miles. 100 Miles; 1986; 11x17.
    4. Kevin "Boomba" Carnes; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-07; 11x17.
    5. Universal Motor Noise, Gerechtigkeits Liga, [& A Play]; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-13; 11x17.
    6. The Witnesses, Boss Hoss; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-05; 6x14.5.
    7. Eyes Of God; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-02; 10.5x12.
    8. Boys 'n' Ghouls! Halloween At Wolfgang's. 3rd Annual Dance [etc.]; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-31; 11x17.
    9. Bird Killers, Sea Hags; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-06; 11x13.
    10. Kerouac: The Essence Of Jack; M-Room; 1411 10th Ave. Oakland, CA; February 14-28, March 1-8; 11x17.
    11. Swim-A-Thon. All Proceeds Go To Gay Games II And San Francisco Arts & Athletics, Inc.; Hamilton Pool; 1900 Geary Blvd. San Francisco, CA; October 13; 11x17.
    12. B.P.M. By Cultural Odyssey, Rhodessa Jones & Idris Ackamoor, Madam Butterfly By Covergirls; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-05; 11x17.
    13. Schrödinger's Cat, Nimbus, Calico Basket; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; October 31; 11x17.
    14. Saqqara Dogs; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-10 -- Saqqara Dogs; DNA Lounge; 375 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-16; 11x17.
    15. Redd Kross, Flying Color, Hanging Party, Shiva Dancing [Siva Dancing]; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-22; 11x17.
    16. Stick Against Stone, The Chills; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-13; 11x17.
    17. The Cat Heads, Stick Against Stone, Tripod Jimmie, Dot 3; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-07; 11x17.
    18. Glorious Din, Paranoid Blue; Artists' Television Access (ATA)/Martin/Weber Gallery; 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-04; 11x17.
    19. Glorious Din, Barnacle Choir (From Santa Cruz), Winnebago Bros (From L.A.), World Of Pooh; Swedish American Hall [Swiss American Hall, sic]; 2174 Market St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-17; 11x17.
    20. Glorious Din; Artists' Television Access (ATA)/Martin/Weber Gallery; 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-04; 11x17.
  - Folder 4, 1984- 1986 (Box 5)
    1. The Invertebrates, Ku Ku Ku; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-18; 11x17.
    2. Benjamin Bossi, Norman Salant Saxophone Duet; Noe Valley Ministry; 1021 Sanchez St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-08; 11x17.
    3. Zula Pool, Elements Of Style; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-15; 11x17.
    4. Malo, Deja Vu; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-04; 11x17.
    5. Invertebrates, Gleaming Spires, Mechanical Bride; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-30; 11x17.
    6. Gone World, Terra Incognita, Terminators Of Endearment, Elliot Schneider, The Naked Into, American Music Club, Joady Guthrie; 16th Note/Firehouse 7; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; May 1; 11x17.
    7. Paranoid Blue, Psychic Orphans; CA; 15x22.
    8. Baseball Zombie; Video Free America; 442 Shotwell St. San Francisco, CA; 1984; 15x21.
    9. Lethal Gospel, The Witnesses, Ultimately Sammy; Club 181; 181 Eddy St. San Francisco, CA; 14x16.5.
    10. [semi-abstract image, possibly a face, with lettering, possibly "Half" printed on large yellow sticker]; 12x12.
    11. Denim TV; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; May 5 -- Denim TV; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; May 9 -- Denim TV; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; May 30; 8.5x14.
    12. Pichote; 1117 Club; 1117 California St. San Francisco, CA; December 17; 11x17.
    13. Science Presents Future; Giftcenter Pavilion; 888 Brannan St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-30; 12.5x19.
  - Folder 5, 1989 (Box 5)
    1. Let's Get Lost; Bell Auditorium; Minneapolis, MN; 1989-07-28; 11x17.
    2. The Crash Dummies; 400 Bar; Minneapolis, MN; 1989-08-15; 11x17.
    3. Widgets; The Uptown; Minneapolis, MN; 1989-08-04; 11x14.5.
  - Folder 1, 1985- 1986 (Map-folder 6)
    1. [many]; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-24; 8.5x21.
    2. Trial; Twin Palms; 44 Brannan St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-16; 20x24.
    3. Impulse F, Monkey Rhythm, Convictions, Denim TV; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-08; 22x17.
    4. David Howard, Keith Haring; Hank Baum Gallery; 2140 Bush St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04; 22x29.
    5. David Howard, Keith Haring; Hank Baum Gallery; 2140 Bush St. San Francisco, CA; March 22, 29 April 5, 12 -- David Howard, Keith Haring; San Francisco Art Institute; 800 Chestnut St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-14; 21x29, 24x33.
    6. Reggae Benefit. MLK. 5 Bands. 6 Sound Systems; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-19; 32x50.
- magazines (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - O+O. No. 1, 1984-02
    Small photocopied zine (8p. folded) containing artwork, fiction and local music news.
  - Wiring Department. “San Francisco Underground ’85.” Empty Milk Bar, 1985
    "Wiring Department" was a relatively professional staple-bound magazine with a number of interviews and show reviews of bands contemporary to the fliers Law collected. There is no date, volume or issue number, nor is there any page numeration. This issue includes short interviews, reviews, and photos with the following complete list: World Of Pooh, Kor-phu, Fang, MDC, Faith No More, Problemist, Asbestos Rockpyle, Dicks, Short Dogs Grow, New Language, MJB, Verbal Abuse, Trial, Ku Ku Ku, Glorious Din, Frightwig, Angst, Fuck Ups, 23 Screams, Mess Tent, Thought Factory, Fade To Black, Drunk Injuns, Tales Of Terror, Morally Bankrupt, Pleasant Day, Tragic Mulatto, Naked Into, Paris Working, Morlocks, Mod Mach, Pray For Rain, Pukes, Dot3, Caroliner Rainbow, Koel Brothers, Smashed Weekend, DJ Lebowitz, DRI, Three Mouse Guitars, Look, Wages Of Sin, Code Of The West, Paranoid Blue, Altar Da Fey, Boss Hoss, Soldiers Of Fortune, Amongst, Stick Against Stone, Dangerous Visions, Tripod Jimmie, Eyes Of God, Acid Chickens, Howie Klein.
    "Wiring Department" was a relatively professional staple-bound magazine with a number of interviews and show reviews of bands contemporary to the fliers Law collected. There is no date, volume or issue number, nor is there any page numeration. This issue includes short interviews, reviews, and photos with the following:
    World Of Pooh, Kor-phu, Fang, MDC, Faith No More, Problemist, Asbestos Rockpyle, Dicks, Short Dogs Grow, New Language, MJB, Verbal Abuse, Trial, Ku Ku Ku, Glorious Din, Frightwig, Angst, Fuck Ups, 23 Screams, Mess Tent, Thought Factory, Fade To Black, Drunk Injuns, Tales Of Terror, Morally Bankrupt, Pleasant Day, Tragic Mulatto, Naked Into, Paris Working, Morlocks, Mod Mach, Pray For Rain, Pukes, Dot3, Caroliner Rainbow, Koel Brothers, Smashed Weekend, DJ Lebowitz, DRI, Three Mouse Guitars, Look, Wages Of Sin, Code Of The West, Paranoid Blue, Altar Da Fey, Boss Hoss, Soldiers Of Fortune, Amongst, Stick Against Stone, Dangerous Visions, Tripod Jimmie, Eyes Of God, Acid Chickens, Howie Klein.
- Berlin exhibition material, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Contains the text written by Law for the exhibition, along with two letters to defunct clubs he attempted to contact (stamped “returned to sender”) about the show.